https://www.euroclonegroup.it/page/privacy_policy

Questo sito utilizza cookie di profilazione propri o di terze parti, per saperne di più clicca qui
Technical Resources
CoA (Certificates of Analysis)
Go
Potrebbe interessarti anche...
Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This page describes how to process personal data of users who visit the site. This is an information that is provided pursuant to art. 13 of Legislative Decree 196/2003 - Code of protection in the matter of personal data - to those who interact with the website of the company EUROCLONE SpA accessible by telematic means starting from the address https://www.euroclonegroup.it/ . The information is provided only for the EUROCLONE SpA website and not for other websites that may be consulted by the user through links. The information is also based on the provisions of Recommendation no. 2/2001 that the European Authorities for the protection of personal data, gathered in the Group established by the art. 29 of the Directive n. 95/46 / EC have adopted on 17/05/2001 to identify some minimum requirements for the collection of personal data online, and in particular, the methods, timing and nature of the information that the holders must provide to users when these they link to web pages regardless of the purpose of the link. The present informative also possesses all the requisites required by the art. 13 of the 2016/679 EU Regulation.
HOLDER OF THE TREATMENT
Following consultation of this site, data relating to identified or identifiable persons may be processed. The data controller is EUROCLONE SpA, with registered office in Pero (MI), Via Figino 22.
DATA PROCESSING PLACE
The data related to the navigation of the site or voluntarily provided by users and treatments related to the services provided take place at the headquarters. The data provided by users are processed by the Data Processor and by the persons in charge in full compliance with the Code.
Data usage
Purpose of the collection of personal data: are collected and recorded only personal data necessary for the purpose for which these data are sent freely by the user.
NAVIGATION DATA
The computer systems and the software components used for the proper functioning of this website acquire, during their normal operation, some data already present in the use of Internet communication protocols. This information is not collected and registered to be associated with identified interested parties, but by their very nature could, through special processing and association with data held by third parties, allow users to be identified. This is information such as domain names used to connect to the site by users and, in any case, they are used for the sole purpose of obtaining anonymous statistical information on the use of the site and to check its correct functioning.
COOKIES AND TAGS
This site uses very common cookies as a marker of a user's identity. The life of cookies is limited to the browsing session, ie closed the Browser (Explorer, Chrome, Mozilla or others), the cookie dies. In some cases cookies are created that have a maximum life time of 2 years, specifically these recorded if you have arrived on our site through the Google search engine and has the express purpose of measuring the effect of advertising campaigns on the Motors of Search. The cookies of this site do not constitute a danger of data acquisition for the computer / browser of the user who accepts them. Within the website some pages are subjected to statistical analysis through "TAGS" specific to the Google Analytics service.
DATA SUPPLIED VOLUNTARILY BY USER
Following the consultation of this site, data allowing the identification of data subjects can be processed. The voluntary and explicit sending of data by completing the form in the CONTACTS section involves the acquisition of the sender's e-mail address and other information such as: Name, Surname, Business name, address, telephone number, fax. Even the optional, explicit and voluntary sending of electronic mail to the addresses indicated on this site involves the subsequent acquisition of the sender's address, necessary to respond to requests, as well as any other personal data included in the message.
DATA PROCESSING METHODS
Personal data are processed with automated tools for the time strictly necessary to achieve the purposes for which they were collected. Specific security measures are observed to prevent data loss, illicit or incorrect use and unauthorized access and more generally for everything concerning the processing of data with such tools.
INTERACTION WITH SOCIAL NETWORK AND EXTERNAL PLATFORMS
These services allow you to make interactions with social networks, or other external platforms, directly from the pages of this website. The interactions and information acquired from this website are in any case subject to the user's privacy settings related to each social network. In the event that an interaction service with social networks is installed, it is possible that, even if users do not use the service, the same collect traffic data relating to the pages in which it is installed.
COMMUNICATION AND DIFFUSION OF DATA
The personal data provided by users who forward requests for information, reports, complaints and sending informative material are used only to respond to the request received and are communicated to third parties in the event that this is necessary for this purpose, or to fulfill to legal obligations. Beyond these cases, the data will not be communicated or disseminated to any other subject, unless explicit consent of the user.
Links to other websites
EUROCLONE SpA can provide on its website some links to third party websites. Since the Company does not control these websites, users are advised to review the privacy policies they enter. These external sites, whose links are present on our site, go beyond the responsibility of the Company
Like button and Facebook social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)
The "Like" button and Facebook social widgets are services of interaction with the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook, Inc. Personal data collected: Cookies and usage data. Place of processing: USA - Privacy Policy
Tweet button and Twitter social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)
The Tweet button and Twitter social widgets are services of interaction with the Twitter social network, provided by Twitter, Inc. Personal data collected: cookies and usage data. Place of processing: USA - Privacy Policy
RIGHTS OF THE INTERESTED
The subjects to whom the personal data refer have the right at any time to obtain confirmation of the existence or otherwise of the same data and to know its content and origin, verify its accuracy or request its integration or updating, or correction (articles 15 and following EU Regulation 2016/679). You have the right to request cancellation, transformation into anonymous form or blocking of data processed in violation of the law, as well as to oppose in any case, for legitimate reasons, to their processing; finally, you have the right to ask to be informed of the existence of adequate guarantees pursuant to art. 46 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 in the case of personal data transferred to a third country or to an international organization, request deletion where possible (right to be forgotten), request treatment limitation, request data portability. The above mentioned requests should be addressed to EUROCLONE SpA, with registered office in Pero (MI), Via Figino 22
Privacy Policy
In questa pagina vengono descritte le modalità di trattamento dei dati personali degli utenti che consultano il sito. Si tratta di un ‘informativa che è resa ai sensi dell’art. 13 del D. Lgs. 196/2003- Codice di protezione in materia di dati personali- a coloro che interagiscono con il sito web della società EUROCLONE SpA accessibile per via telematica a partire dall’indirizzo https://www.euroclonegroup.it/. L’informativa è resa solo per il sito di EUROCLONE SpA e non anche per altri siti web eventualmente consultati dall’utente tramite link. L’informativa si ispira anche a quanto sancito nella Raccomandazione n. 2/2001 che le Autorità Europee per la protezione dei dati personali, riunite nel Gruppo istituito dall’art. 29 della Direttiva n. 95/46/CE hanno adottato il 17/05/2001 per individuare alcuni requisiti minimi per la raccolta dei dati personali on line, e in particolare, le modalità, i tempi e la natura delle informazioni che i titolari devono fornire agli utenti quando questi si collegano a pagine web a prescindere dagli scopi del collegamento. La presente informativa, inoltre possiede tutti i requisiti richiesti dall’art. 13 del Regolamento UE 2016/679.
TITOLARE DEL TRATTAMENTO
A seguito della consultazione di questo sito possono essere trattati dati relativi a persone identificate o identificabili. Il titolare del trattamento dati è EUROCLONE SpA, con sede in Pero (MI), Via Figino 22.
LUOGO DI TRATTAMENTO DEI DATI
I dati legati alla navigazione del sito o volontariamente forniti dagli utenti ed i trattamenti connessi ai servizi erogati hanno luogo presso la sede. I dati forniti dagli utenti sono trattati dal Responsabile del trattamento e dagli incaricati nel pieno rispetto del Codice.
Utilizzo dei dati
Finalità della raccolta dei dati personali: sono raccolti e registrati esclusivamente i dati personali necessari alla finalità per la quale tali dati sono inviati liberamente dall’utente.
DATI DI NAVIGAZIONE
I sistemi informatici ed i componenti software impiegati per il corretto funzionamento di questo sito web acquisiscono, durante il loro normale esercizio, alcuni dati già presenti nell'uso dei protocolli di comunicazione di Internet. Tali informazioni non sono raccolte e registrate per essere associate a interessati identificati, ma per loro stessa natura potrebbero, attraverso particolari elaborazioni ed associazioni con dati detenuti da terzi, permettere di identificare gli utenti. Si tratta di informazioni quali nomi a dominio utilizzati per la connessione al sito da parte degli utenti e, comunque, esse sono utilizzate al solo fine di ricavare informazioni statistiche anonime sull'uso del sito e per controllarne il corretto funzionamento.
COOKIES E TAGS
Il presente sito utilizza dei comunissimi cookies come marcatore dell’identità di un utente. La vita dei cookies è limitata alla sessione di navigazione, ossia chiuso il Browser (Explorer, Chrome, Mozilla o altri), il cookie muore. In alcuni casi vengono creati cookies che hanno un tempo massimo di vita di 2 Anni, nello specifico questi registrato se siete arrivati sul nostro sito tramite il motore di ricerca Google e ha l'espresso scopo di misurare l'effetto delle campagne pubblicitarie sui Motori di Ricerca. I cookies del presente sito non costituiscono pericolo di acquisizione dati per il computer/browser dell’utente che li accetta. All’interno del sito web alcune pagine sono sottoposte ad analisi statistica attraverso “TAGS” specifici del servizio Google Analytics.
DATI FORNITI VOLONTARIAMENTE DALL'UTENTE
In seguito alla consultazione di questo sito possono essere trattati dati che consentono l’identificazione degli interessati. L’invio volontario ed esplicito di dati attraverso la compilazione del form presente nella sezione CONTATTI comporta l’acquisizione dell’indirizzo e-mail del mittente e di altre informazioni quali : Nome, Cognome, Ragione sociale, indirizzo, telefono, fax. Anche l’invio facoltativo, esplicito e volontario di posta elettronica agli indirizzi indicati su questo sito comporta la successiva acquisizione dell’indirizzo del mittente, necessario per rispondere alle richieste, nonché degli eventuali altri dati personali inseriti nella missiva.
MODALITA’ DI TRATTAMENTO DEI DATI
I dati personali sono trattati con strumenti automatizzati per il tempo strettamente necessario a conseguire gli scopi per cui sono stati raccolti. Specifiche misure di sicurezza sono osservate per prevenire la perdita dei dati, usi illeciti o non corretti ed accessi non autorizzati ed più in generale per tutto ciò che concerne il trattamento dei dati con tali strumenti.
INTERAZIONE CON SOCIAL NETWORK E PIATTAFORME ESTERNE
Questi servizi permettono di effettuare interazioni con i social network, o con altre piattaforme esterne, direttamente dalle pagine di questo sito web. Le interazioni e le informazioni acquisite da questo sito web sono in ogni caso soggette alle impostazioni privacy dell'utente relative ad ogni social network. Nel caso in cui sia installato un servizio di interazione con i social network, è possibile che, anche nel caso gli utenti non utilizzino il servizio, lo stesso raccolga dati di traffico relativi alle pagine in cui è installato.
COMUNICAZIONE E DIFFUSIONE DEI DATI
I dati personali forniti dagli utenti che inoltrano richieste di informazioni, segnalazioni, lamentele e di invio di materiale informativo sono utilizzati al solo fine di rispondere alla richiesta ricevuta e sono comunicati a terzi nel caso in cui ciò sia necessario a tale scopo, o per adempiere ad obblighi di legge. Al di là di tali casi, i dati non saranno comunicati né diffusi a nessun altro soggetto, salvo consenso esplicito dell’utente.
Link ad altri siti internet
EUROCLONE SpA può fornire sul proprio sito web alcuni link a siti web di terzi. Dal momento che la Società non controlla tali siti web, si consiglia agli utenti di esaminare le informative sulla privacy in essi inserite. Tali siti esterni, i cui collegamenti sono presenti nel nostro sito, vanno al di là della responsabilità della Società
Pulsante Mi Piace e widget sociali di Facebook (Facebook, Inc.)
Il pulsante "Mi Piace" e i widget sociali di Facebook sono servizi di interazione con il social network Facebook, forniti da Facebook, Inc. Dati personali raccolti: Cookie e Dati di utilizzo. Luogo del trattamento: USA - Privacy Policy
Pulsante Tweet e widget sociali di Twitter (Twitter, Inc.)
Il pulsante Tweet e i widget sociali di Twitter sono servizi di interazione con il social network Twitter, forniti da Twitter, Inc. Dati personali raccolti: cookie e dati di utilizzo. Luogo del trattamento: USA - Privacy Policy
DIRITTI DEGLI INTERESSATI
I soggetti cui si riferiscono i dati personali hanno il diritto in qualunque momento di ottenere la conferma dell’esistenza o meno dei medesimi dati e di conoscerne il contenuto e l’origine, verificarne l’esattezza o chiederne l’integrazione o l’aggiornamento, oppure la rettificazione (artt. 15 e seguenti Regolamento UE 2016/679). Si ha il diritto di chiedere la cancellazione, la trasformazione in forma anonima o il blocco dei dati trattati in violazione di legge, nonché di opporsi in ogni caso, per motivi legittimi, al loro trattamento; infine si ha diritto di chiedere di essere informato dell’esistenza di garanzie adeguate ai sensi dell’art. 46 del Regolamento (UE) 2016/679 in caso di dati personali trasferiti a un paese terzo o ad un’organizzazione internazionale, chiedere la cancellazione ove possibile (diritto all’oblio), chiedere la limitazione del trattamento, chiedere la portabilità dei dati. Le richieste sopra menzionate vanno rivolte a EUROCLONE SpA, con sede in Pero (MI), Via Figino 22
Euroclone S.p.A. Società a Socio Unico
Via Figino, 20/22
20016 Pero (MI)
Loading tweets by @Euroclone SpA...
Monthly Newsletter
Subscribe to our newsletter and stay up to date with the latest news and deals!
SUBSCRIBE
2014 © Euroclone S.p.A. Società a Socio Unico. ALL Rights Reserved
P.IVA/CF 08126390155 Reg. Imp. MI - REA 1208538
Privacy Policy | Disclaimer
